

+1 647 906 5855

rosynguyen278@gmail.com

North York, M3J 0B8, Canada

www.rosyhnguyen.me

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

I have a strong background in **Product/ UX Design** and **Front end development**. I have been designing digital experiences for **3+ years** across a variety of industries in Canada, Malaysia, and Vietnam. My love for minimalist design and human-centered approach keeps me inspired, together with a serious obssession for volunteering and photography.

VOLUNTEER

- Seneca College:
 Mentor for 5 first year students,
 member of Leadership Program in
 2019 and 2020
- Jaipur Literature Festival 2019: Volunteered photographer
- Nuit Blanche Toronto 2018: Hallway monitor
- AIESEC: Global Talent, Volunteer

SKILLS

- Leadership
- Teamwork
- Time Management
- HTML, CSS, JS, Bootstrap, Github
- Blog writing

TOOLS

- Adobe XD, Figma, Sketch, InVision
- Adobe InDesign, Photoshop,
 Illustrator, AfterEffect, Premiere

CERTIFICATES

- Interaction Design Foundation "How to create a UX Portfolio" March 2020
- Fulbright Economics Program:
 The Scholarship Summer 2015

ALSO

I am a passionate amateur photographer with **1+ million** views on Unsplash (unsplash.com/@rosy_h_nguyen)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Community Coordinator

Toronto, Canada

DesignX Canada/ Part time/ Feb 2019 - Present

- Foster healthy discussions within Slack platform to engage the global community of 4000+ designers with the key focus on Canadian market.
- Run weekly surveys and polls to stay on top of community engagement.

Interactive Media Design Tutor

Toronto, Canada

Seneca College/ Part time/ Sep 2019 - Apr 2020

 Prepare lessons and provide academic assistance on Web Development (HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, GitHub) and Graphic design (Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign)

Product Designer

Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

Inmagine Group/ Full time/ Sep 2016 - Dec 2017

Product Executive

- Redesign product strategy, price strategy, license policy and website for StockUnlimited.com.
- Develop, monitor global partnership programs for StockUnlimited.com, especially North America and EUR market.

Product Designer

- Run user interview, competitor analysis, testing sessions and regular design reviews for a new mobile app named PopDQ
- Collaborate with developers and creative team within weekly sprint cycles.
- Work closely with the founder to launch PopDQ in App Store & Google Play.

Product Manager

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

UNESCO/ Full time / Dec 2014 - Aug 2016

- Manage 25 university seminars and 3 conferences for 17,000 students
- Monitor cooperation between UNESCO-CEP and Sponsor Organizations.

EDUCATION

Interactive Media Design International Business Diploma Bachelor Seneca College, Toronto, Canada University of Economics UEH, Vietnam Sept 2018 - Apr 2020 Sept 2012 - Apr 2016